{
    "data":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What is the CSS property for changing the size of an element?",
            "answer": "width",
            "a": "size",
            "b": "weight",
            "c": "width",
            "d": "wide"
          },
          {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What is the CSS property for containing the exceedings of elements in a container?",
            "answer": "flex-wrap",
            "a": "flex",
            "b": "flex-direction",
            "c": "contain",
            "d": "flex-wrap"
          },
          {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the closing tag for the HTML structure?",
            "answer": "</html>",
            "a": "<html/>",
            "b": "<html>",
            "c": "</html>",
            "d": "</Html>"
          },
          {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What is the CSS property for curving the sharp edges of an element?",
            "answer": "border-radius",
            "a": "border-line",
            "b": "curver",
            "c": "border-arc",
            "d": "border-radius"
          },
          {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What is the difference between inline CSS, embedded CSS, and external CSS?",
            "answer": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed outside the `<head>` tag, and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
            "a": "Inline CSS is placed outside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
            "b": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
            "c": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed outside the `<head>` tag, and external CSS is placed in a separate file.",
            "d": "Inline CSS is placed inside the HTML document, embedded CSS is placed inside the `<head>` tag,and external CSS is placed in the same file."
          },
          {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Which of the following tag is used to embed css in html page?",
            "answer": "<style></style>",
            "a": "<css>",
            "b": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
            "c": "<script></script>",
            "d": "<style></style>"
          },
          {
            "id": 7,
            "question": " Which of the following CSS selectors are used to specify a group of elements?",
            "answer": "class",
            "a": "tag",
            "b": "id",
            "c": "class",
            "d": "id and class"
          },
          {
            "id": 8,
            "question": " Which of the following has introduced text, list, box, margin, border, color, and background properties?",
            "answer": "CSS",
            "a": "HTML",
            "b": "PHP",
            "c": "CSS",
            "d": "JAVASCRIPT"
          },
          {
            "id": 9,
            "question": " Which of these is not a programming languages?",
            "answer": "CSS",
            "a": "JAVA",
            "b": "PHP",
            "c": "CSS",
            "d": "JAVASCRIPT"
          },
          {
            "id": 10,
            "question": " Which of the following is the correct syntax to link an external style sheet in the HTML file?",
            "answer": " <link rel=”stylesheet” href=”style.css” />",
            "a": " <link rel=”stylesheet” href=”style.css” />",
            "b": "<link rel=”stylesheet” src=”style.css” />",
            "c": "<style rel=”stylesheet” src=”style.css” />",
            "d": " <style rel=”stylesheet” link=”style.css” />"
          },
          {
            "id": 11,
            "question": " which of these is a type of styling",
            "answer": " all of the above",
            "a": "inline styling",
            "b": "embedded styling",
            "c": "external styling",
            "d": " all of the above"
          },
          {
            "id": 12,
            "question": " which of css properties is used to change the text color ",
            "answer": " color",
            "a": "font-size",
            "b": "color",
            "c": "background-color",
            "d": " all of the above"
          },
          {
            "id": 13,
            "question": " which of css properties is used to change the text colour ",
            "answer": " color",
            "a": "font-size",
            "b": "color",
            "c": "background-color",
            "d": " all of the above"
          },
          {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "In building a website, we must first?",
            "answer": "boxify",
            "a": "call display flex",
            "b": "boxify",
            "c": "do the styling",
            "d": "Do justify content"
          },
          {
            "id": 15,
            "Question": "_____ is the major difference between Notepad and Visual Studio Code",
            "answer": "VSCode allows you use intelliscence while Notepad does not",
            "a": "Visual Studio Code is for cuilding websites while notepad is used for webApp",
            "b": "Notepad is used for CSS while VSCode is used for HTML ",
            "c": "Notepad allows you use intelliscence while VSCode does not",
            "d": "VSCode allows you use intelliscence while Notepad does not"
          },
          {
            "id": 16,
            "Question": "Which of the following statement(s) is/are correct?",
            "answer": "CSS is only used for styling",
            "a": "HTML is only used for building Websites",
            "b": "CSS is only used for styling",
            "c": "Microsoft Excel is a text editor ",
            "d": "HTML is used for styling"
          },
          {
            "id": 17,
            "Question": "We create _______ in a folder",
            "answer": "files",
            "a": "cells",
            "b": "components",
            "c": "files",
            "d": "tables"
          },
          {
            "id": 18,
            "Question": "Which is the first component of a website?",
            "answer": "Header",
            "a": "Body",
            "b": "Header",
            "c": "Footer",
            "d": "Sider"
          },
          {
            "id": 19,
            "Question": "HTML tags are usually enclosed in?",
            "answer": "Angular brackets",
            "a": "Curly braces",
            "b": "Square brackets",
            "c": "parenthesis",
            "d": "Angular brackets"
          },
          {
            "id": 20,
            "Question": "all HTML tags are closed",
            "answer": "False",
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False",
            "c": "Maybe",
            "d": "Certainly"
          },
          {
            "id": 21,
            "Question": "In order to style a div in html, we give it a _________",
            "answer": "class",
            "a": "class",
            "b": "color",
            "c": "width",
            "d": "height"
          },
          {
            "id": 22,
            "Question": "Carpenter is to Hammer and Nail as Developer is to?",
            "answer": "Laptop and Smart Phone",
            "a": "Rows and columns",
            "b": "Text and Images",
            "c": "Laptop and Smart Phone",
            "d": "Signs and Symbols"
          },
          {
            "id": 23,
            "Question": "The title tag is enclosed in what tag?",
            "answer": "Head tag",
            "a": "Head tag",
            "b": "Body tag",
            "c": "div tag",
            "d": "None of the above"
          },
          {
            "id": 24,
            "Question": "Majority of our codes are found in the?",
            "answer": "Body tag",
            "a": "Head tag",
            "b": "Body tag",
            "c": "div tag",
            "d": "None of the above"
          }
        
    ]
}